osgeo.org 2006-10-12

# LegalNotices

**IMPORTANT:** BY USING OR ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE.

## 1\. Commitment

In order to make various features and functions of the website (" **Site** ") available to authorized users (" **You** "), CollabNet, Inc. (" **CollabNet** ") collects certain information about You and your use of the Site, including, but not limited to, your first and last name, the name of your organization, if any, your username and your e-mail address (" **Personal Information** "). CollabNet is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any Personal Information You share with us. CollabNet established this privacy policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") so that You can understand the care with which CollabNet intends to treat your Personal Information.

## 2\. Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on the Site homepage so You are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use the Personal Information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify You via e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use the Personal Information in this different manner.

## 3\. Limited Use of Cookies

The Site makes limited use of "session" cookies. When you visit the Site, a cookie is written to save your session ID. You must enable cookies in your browser in order to log into and use the Site. The information we collect and analyze through such cookies is used anonymously, and in the aggregate, to improve our service and to understand Site traffic patterns.

## 4\. Security

CollabNet has taken appropriate and reasonable steps to protect the Personal Information that You share with CollabNet from unauthorized access or disclosure. CollabNet will not share your Personal Information with third parties without your advance opt-in consent unless such release is legally required.

CollabNet uses Secure Socket Layer (" **SSL** ") technology on this Site. SSL establishes a secure connection between the user and the server and uses a private key to encrypt data that is transferred across this connection.

## 5\. Open Source and Community Projects

If this Site is an open source or community source site (" **Open Project** ") and You choose to participate in an open source or community source project, whether by contributing code, participating in mailing lists or joining discussion forums, your participation is public and your privacy cannot be protected to the extent that You provide Personal Information such as your e-mail address. To the extent that You contribute code, information, articles or other material to an Open Project on this Site containing Personal Information, we cannot protect the privacy of such Personal Information and such material may be provided to others under the Site's Terms of Service and applicable licenses.

## 6\. Accuracy

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of the Personal Information You supply to us. You can update and modify the Personal Information at any time through the "Edit Profile" tool.

## 7\. Consent

By using or accessing the Site, You acknowledge and agree that CollabNet's collection and use of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and CollabNet's operation and provision of the Site, as contemplated under this Privacy Policy, is not a breach of your right of privacy, publicity, or any other right related to protection of personal data, whether in equity, law, contract, or otherwise. You hereby waive any and all such claims or rights of action, whether foreseen or unforeseen, so long as the Personal Information is collected, stored, and used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## 8\. Questions or Comments

If You have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [feedback@collab.net](mailto:feedback@collab.net).
